Mighty Little Defenders 11 – New Wild Cosmos.
Trouble’s Brewing
Episode 15
let me go
I thought you were a good person before
I didn’t expect you to be a big bad guy who kidnaps children.
save me
You bad guy, let her go.
I advise you not to meddle in other people’s business
or
Just pretend you didn’t see it
how?
say it again
Let her go
Really love to be a hero
Goodbye then
A boy who doesn’t know the heights of the world
Uncle, the boy is not going to hold back
Let’s go quickly
my doll
What are you doing? It’s too dangerous.
Get it and go quickly
who are you
How dare you act wild in my place
Listen up, our names are Weslie
and Wolffy
It’s okay now
Thanks
You said before that that man is not your father
What on earth is going on?
Mom said you can’t talk to strangers
But we are all good people
No
You look like one
bad guy
Then you can tell me
Thank you for helping me get the doll
But you catch me
Also a bad guy
It seems she won’t say anything
Weslie are you hungry?
Yes, yes, I’m really hungry
So what shall we eat?
Grass cakes, vanilla pancakes
and delicious seaweed soup
Let’s go do the quest to exchange for food.
wait for me
boss, bad
Xiao Mei was kidnapped
useless stuff
Nothing can be done well
Who ruined my good deeds?
Could it be
Blue Scarf who destroys the city alone?
No
They seem to be called Weslie and Wolffy
What a nobody?
dares to disturb me
Where is my majesty?
you
Boss, please spare me.
You must bring that Xiao Mei back to me
Guaranteed completion of tasks
Collect parts to exchange for food
We just dug out this few parts.
look
I dug up so many parts
This time we
can definitely have a full meal
Very good
What, that’s all?
Really
So many parts in exchange for so little food?
It would be nice if we could have something to eat.
Then eat quickly
Give it all to me. Aren’t you hungry?
I’m just a woolen doll. I don’t need to eat.
I’m not hungry either
Let’s eat together
Running away in fear all day long
It’s been a while since I sat down for a full meal
Why are you running away?
Why do those bad guys want to catch you?
I used to live well with my mother
Who knows one day
Guangzong’s men suddenly broke into my house
Smashed and rummaged
Mom plays a game with you
Mom believes you can do it
Found them. They’re here.
Knock the door open quickly
I’ll deal with them
You go to that place first and wait for me
Mom
But not long after
The bad guys found me soon
Keep chasing me
But my mom is still there waiting for me
I must go to the place agreed with my mom
This doll is my most precious thing
I give the doll as payment
Please escort me to that place
okay?
I
We are both hungry now
Not solving the problem of eating
She is also starving and suffering even if she follows us.
How about we take her to a safe place first?
Let’s take a long-term view later
Finally found you
It’s the robber from before
Run quickly
Don’t even think about escaping from me again
Catch them quickly
He is much stronger than before
I advise you to surrender obediently.
Our boss’s favorite prey
No one can take it away
She’s not prey, she’s free
You want to catch such a kid?
Where has your conscience gone?
you
How many bottles of water is conscience worth?
Run quickly
You can’t escape
Sleep together in this desert
Get out of the way
Wolffy, are you okay?
Wolffy
Don’t worry, everyone has a share
Weslie, get out of the way.
No
this time
Let me protect you
What
who is
Such a powerful attack? Is it
Sand Shadow
Yes, it’s them. run quickly
Darn it, I’ll be back
What a nostalgic line
thank you for saving us
this weapon
They are the highest reward?
Who are you? Let go of Xiao Mei
Brother Weslie
Xiao Mei
Xiao Mei, I promise you now
I will definitely take you to your destination
To be continued